{
    "id": "6c7cbe365ad3460a9e1e3664745c3a93",
    "title": "Active and Passive Voice",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5057c8d28a864c248e1fc9af0baf1661",
            "title": "Active And Passive Voice",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "They printed these books. These books ………………….. by them.",
                    "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after was/were.",
                    "answers": [
                        "are printed",
                        "have been printed",
                        "were printed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Clean the room. Let the room …………………….",
                    "description": "Passive forms of imperatives are made with be + past participle. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "cleaned",
                        "be cleaned",
                        "is cleaned"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher reprimanded the boy. The boy …………………….. by the teacher.",
                    "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after was/were.",
                    "answers": [
                        "reprimanded",
                        "was reprimanded",
                        "has reprimanded"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They will announce the results in the afternoon. Results ……………………….. in the afternoon.",
                    "description": "In the simple future, the passive form is made by putting will + be before the past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will announced",
                        "are announced",
                        "will be announced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Everybody hates him. He …………………….. by everybody.",
                    "description": "In the simple present tense, we make the passive form with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "hates",
                        "is hating",
                        "is hated"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The monkey is eating a banana. A banana …………………….. by the monkey.",
                    "description": "In the present continuous, we make the passive form by putting is/am/are + being before the past participle form of the verb. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "is eaten",
                        "is being eaten",
                        "was being eaten"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The government will build a bridge. A bridge …………………….. by the government.",
                    "description": "In the simple future, the passive form is made by putting will + be before the past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will be build",
                        "will be built",
                        "will be building"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She gave me a book. I …………………… a book by her.",
                    "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after was/were.",
                    "answers": [
                        "gave",
                        "was given",
                        "have given"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She cheated him. He ……………………. by her.",
                    "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after was/were.",
                    "answers": [
                        "was cheated",
                        "has cheated",
                        "had cheated"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have sent the parcel. The parcel ………………………….. by me.",
                    "description": "In the present perfect tense, the passive form is made by putting has/have + been before the past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "has sent",
                        "has been sent",
                        "have been sent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has composed a song. A song ………………………. by him.",
                    "description": "In the present perfect tense, the passive form is made by putting has/have + been before the past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is composed",
                        "has been composed",
                        "is being composed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher asked him to get out. He ………………………. by the teacher to get out.",
                    "description": "In the simple past, we make the passive form by putting the past participle form of the verb after was/were.",
                    "answers": [
                        "was asked",
                        "has asked",
                        "has been asked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}